Guide to the Margaret Mary Nicholson papers, 1901-1981 MS0256.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographs, 1901-1955; MS0256 Series 5; 0.5 Linear feet
  - Oversize Documents: La Sociedad Mexicana de Pediatria, 01/26/1950; MS0256 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Oversize Documents: Pro Ecclesia et Pontifice, 01/15/1974; MS0256 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Oversize Documents: Award of Merit, District of Columbia Chapter, American Academy of Pediatrics, 04/28/1979; MS0256 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Oversize Documents: American Medical Association, Physicians Recognition Award, 05/01/1981; MS0256 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Oversize Documents: Fifty Year Club of American Medicine, undated; MS0256 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Oversize Documents: Hahnemann Hospital (Washington, D.C.) 1930-59 Head of Pediatrics, undated; MS0256 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 28)